// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "There are 4 strawberries, 3 apples, 2 oranges and 1 each of 3 other varieties of fruits. The number of ways of selecting one fruit of each kind is",
    answer: "4!",
    options: ["10!", "9!", "4!", "5!"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Find the probability of getting 3 on rolling a die ?",
    answer: "1/6",
    options: ["1/6", "5/6", "2/6", "4/7"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "A box contains 90 discs numbered 1 to 90. One disc is drawn at random from the box. What is the probability that is bears a perfect square ?",
    answer: "1/10",
    options: ["1/9", "1/10", "1/12", "3/11"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "A die randomly tossed. What is the probability of getting, a multiple of 2.",
    answer: "1/2",
    options: ["1/3", "1/2", "2/3", "3/2"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "2 cards are randomly drawn from the deck of cards. What is the probability that either both are red or both are kings.",
    answer: "55/221",
    options: ["55/225", "55/221", "48/131", "54/223"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "Ajay rolled two dice together. What is the probability that first dice showed a multiple of 3 and the second dice showed an even number?",
    answer: "1/6",
    options: ["1/6", "1/3", "5/6", "1/9"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The sample space of four coins tossed together is:",
    answer: "16",
    options: ["8", "64", "32", "16"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "The probability of Sita, Gita and Mita passing a test is 60%, 40% and 20% respectively. What is the probability that at Sita and Gita will pass the test and Mita will not?",
    answer: "19.2%",
    options: ["38.4%", "60%", "4.8%", "19.2%"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "Two unbiased dice are rolled simultaneously. Find the probability of getting sum greater than 5.",
    answer: "13/18",
    options: ["13/18", "23/26", "7/9", "5/9"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "A bag contains coins of one rupee, two rupee & five rupees. The total money in the bag is Rs. 120. If the total number of one rupee and two rupee coins are 35 and in ratio of coins is 2 : 5. Find the probability of getting a 5 rupee coin if a coin is randomly picked from the bag?",
    answer: "12/47",
    options: [
      "2/7",
      "5/7",
      "5/47",
      "12/47",
    ],
  },
];
